http://www.sofe.org/about-us/privacy-policy.html

Career Development Seminar
Continuing Regulatory Education (CRE)
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets how SOFE uses and protects any personal information that you provide SOFE when you use this website. SOFE is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. When we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified, you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
SOFE may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you agree with any changes made to the policy. This policy is effective from September 27, 2010.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name and job title
contact information including email address
demographic information such as postal code, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information in order to understand your needs and provide you with better service, and for the following additional reasons:
Internal record keeping.
Improvements to our products and services.
Promotional uses, such as alerting you to availability of new products and services, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting.
From time to time, we may also use your information for market research purposes. As a part of this research, we may attempt to contact you by email, phone, fax or mail.
We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.
With your consent, we may provide your information to our third party partners for marketing or promotional purposes.
We will never sell your information.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being viewed and used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over any other websites. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting other websites. SOFE also does not govern other websites by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and view the privacy statement applicable to the website you are visiting.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anyone for direct marketing purposes
If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at info@SOFE.org, or by updating your personal profile.
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to SOFE, 7044 S. 13th St., Oak Creek, WI 53154.
If you believe that any information we are holding is incorrect or incomplete, please write to us at the above address or send us an email. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
SOFE 3505 Vernon Woods Road
Summerfield, NC 27358
Tel: 336-365-4640 Fax: 336-644-6205
About Us
Board of Governors
Executive Committee
State Chairs
Headquarters Staff
Continuing Regulatory Education (CRE)
